Guide to the George Mason University Libraries records, 1949-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Library Director, 1958-2001
  - Subseries 1.5: Charlene Hurt, 1973-1999
    - Association for Library Collections and Technical Services annual conference, 1992 June 29 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries (ASERL), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries (ASERL), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries (ASERL), 1997 February 22-24 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Director's roundtable discussion, Charleston, South Carolina
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries (ASERL) statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Audiovisual services, 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Automated Library Information System (ALIS), undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Automated library systems, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Automated library system, ALIS implementation survey, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Automated library system, ALIS replacement, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Automated library system procurement request capital outlay funds: Data process, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Automated library systems serials automation project, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Automation consultants / ALA, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Biology 326 animal physiology, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Bibliographic instruction, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Biennium budget proposal capital outlay request, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Biennium operating budget proposal, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Budget analysis, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Budget information, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Budget information, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Budget submissions, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Budgets and notes, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Building services, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Business trips and mileage totals, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Camera books / slide books, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Campus training group, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Capcon, 1982-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Capcon, Union list of serials, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Card catalog freeze, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Card catalog freeze task force, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Carpet replacement Library I and II, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - CAUSE, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1995 November 29-December 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Cause/CNI, 1996 September 10-13 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - CD biology, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - CD Rom database brochures, 1980s (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Ceremonial occasions (fliers and invitations), 1988-1995 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Chadwick-Healey, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Charlene Hurt, 1997 September 9 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Farewell Ceremony
    - Charlene Hurt, 1990-1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Letters in thanks, request letters for conferences and presentations, and other material
    - Charlene Hurt, personal and career accomplishments, 1984-1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Charlene Hurt, 1982-1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Recommendation letters
    - Chronological Files, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 January-February (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 March (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 April (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 May (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 June (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 July (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 August-September (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 October (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Chronological Files, 1987 December (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 January-February (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 March (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 April-May (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 June-July (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 July-August (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 August (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 September (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 October (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 November (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Chronological Files, 1988 December (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 January (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 February-March (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 April-May (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 June-July (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 July (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 August-September (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 September-October (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 October (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 November (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Chronological Files, 1989 December (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 January (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 February (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 March-April (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 May (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 June-July (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 July (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 August (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 September (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 September (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 October-November (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Chronological Files, 1990 December (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 January (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 January (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 February (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 March (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 March (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 April (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 May (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 June (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 July (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 August (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 August-September (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 September (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 September (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 October (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 November (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Chronological Files, 1991 December (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 January (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 February (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 March (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 April-May (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 June-July (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 August (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 August (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 August (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 September (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 October (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Chronological Files, 1992 November-December (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Chronological Files, 1993 April 7 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Collection development, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - The Computer Company, Richmond, Virginia, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Connecting Virginia to the world of information, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Core library proposal, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Alana Ho, 1984-1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Andrew Soil, Assistant Vice President for Business and Finance, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Biology department, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Bristol Community College, Hank Ingles, 1996 June (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, building and grounds, 1982-1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Center for Applied Research and Development in Education, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Center for Conflict Resolution, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Center for Community College Education, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Center for Innovative Technology, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Center for Interactive Educational Technology, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Center for Interactive Management, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Center for Public Choice, 1986-1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Center for the Study of Constitutional Rights, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Centers and Institutes at GMU, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Charlene Hurt, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, City of Fairfax, 1994 September 21 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Clara Lovett, Provost, 1988-1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Clara Lovett, Provost (A), 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Clara Lovett, Provost (A), 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Clara Lovett, Provost (B), 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Clara Lovett, Provost (CH), 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, College of Education and Human Services, Larry Bowen, Dean, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, communication network services, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, community relations, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Computer Emergency Response Team (CERT), 1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, computer networking services, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, conflict clinic, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, continuing education, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, contractors, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, cultural diversity, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, cultural diversity, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, cultural studies (information technology strand, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Data phase users group, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Data touch, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, David J. King, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, David J. King, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, David J. King, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, David J. King, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, David J. King, Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, David Potter, Dean College of Arts and Sciences, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, David Potter, Dean College of Arts and Sciences, 1987-1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, David Potter, Provost, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, David Rossell, Assistant Provost for Administration and Budget, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, David Rossell, Assistant Provost for Administration and Budget, 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, departmental accreditation, 1986-1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Distributed University, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Donald J. Mash, Vice President for Administration, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Donald J. Mash, Vice President for Administration, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Drexler Technology Corporation lasercard, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Ed Delaney, Vice President for Institutional Planning and Research, 1982-1992 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Educational technology group (EDUCOM), Fred Rossini, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Elsa Althen, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Elsa Althen, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, executive assistant to the President William H. Cohn, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Florence Landon, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Floine Graham, Associate Vice President for Administration and Special Projects (Economic Bridge department), 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Fred Rossini, Provost, 1989-1994 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Fred Rossini, Provost, 1990-1995 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Fred Rossini, Provost, 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Fred Siff, Vice President for Computing and Information Systems, 1983-1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Frederick H. Siff, Vice President, UCIS, 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, H. Randall Edwards, Executive Vice President for Administration, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Inlex, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Institute for Advanced Study with the Integrative Sciences, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Institute for the Arts, 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Institute for Computational Sciences and Informatics, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Institute for Humane Studies, 1985-1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Institute of Public Policy, 1973-1996 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Instructional Development Office, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research (ICPSR), 1982-1992 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Internal control guidance manual, 1987-1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, James J. Fletcher, Associate Provost and Dean for Undergraduate Studies, 1985-1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, James Renick, Vice Provost, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Jamie Coniglio (for CH), 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, John Moore, Director International Institute, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Dr. John O'Connor, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Dr. John O'Connor, Intern Vice Provost for Information Technology and Services, 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Kathy Perry, Assistant Provost, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Krasnow Institute, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Larry Czarda, Executive Vice President Finance and Planning, 1985-1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Law School, 1985-1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Library visitors, 1992-1995 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Mark Flynn, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Marvin Tatum, 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Maurice Scherrens, Executive Vice President for Finance and Planning, 1982-1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, microcomputers, software, BRS, After Dark, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, microcomputers, software, TeleVideo Systems, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1985-1990 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Mitre (GMU, Mitre, FCPL network), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, National Technical Information Service (NTIS) RFP, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Oakton and Fenwick partnership, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Office for Intellectual Freedom (ALA), 1986-1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      J. Krug and FBI letters
    - Correspondence, Office of International Programs and service, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Phi Beta Kappa, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, print services, 1991-1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, public relations, 1986 October 31 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      Risk analysis questionnaire
    - Correspondence, Robinson professors, 1987-1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, SACS, 1986-1992 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, School of Business, 1988-1990 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, School of Information Technology and Engineering (SITE), 1987-1994 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, School of Nursing, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Shenandoah University, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      Sociological abstracts
    - Correspondence, social work (HIV/AIDS resources), 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, software productivity consortium, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Stan Taylor, Associate Vice President for Operational Services, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Steven Diner, 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Susan Haynes, Associate Librarian for Collection Services, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Susan Swope, Vice Provost and Registrar, 1987-1994 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, systems science, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, University advancement, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, University relations, 1984-1995 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Wade Gilley, 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Creating a database, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Curriculum library, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum library, 1987-1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Data touch, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Digital archives, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Digitizing project, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Educom, 1990-1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Educom, 1995 October 30 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Educom, 1996 October 9-11 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Educom NLII meeting, New Orleans, 1997 February 2-4 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Educom NLII meeting, New Orleans, 1997 February 2-4 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Evaluation of audiovisual resources and services at Fenwick Library, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Faculty VIP tours, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - FAXON, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - FAXON, 1990-1994 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Fenwick Library Cultural Diversity Committee, 1991 September 23 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Fenwick Library program proposed, 1982-1986 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Fenwick Library space, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - The first year plan, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Floor plan and environmental conditions, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Galvin proposal, electronic information storage, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - George Mason University infrastructure project requirements briefing, 1993 May 27 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Government articles, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Grievance panel, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Guide to performance evaluation, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Inspection of new tower, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - IPAC, 1996 September 20 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Itinerary for Charlene Hurt, University of South Florida visit, 1997 April 24-25 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - John Warfield, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - LAC / SCHEV Secretary Finley, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - LAC / SCHEV meeting, Norfolk, Virginia, 1995 June 8-9 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Library systems, 1982-1984 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - "The making of America: creating electronic pathways to our heritage", Cornell digitization project, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Maps, placement within library, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Memorandums from Charlene Hurt, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Metropolitan Washington Library Council, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Microforms, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - National Federation of Abstracting Services, DC, 1995 February 27-March 1 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - National Technical Information Service (NTIS), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - National Technical Information Service (NTIS), 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - National Technical Information Service (NTIS) end user training, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - National Technical Information Service (NTIS) RFP, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - National Library of Medicine, 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - NOVA online library circulation system, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - OCLC Users Council meeting, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Office of affirmative action, Earl Ingram, 1988-1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Office of research, 1985-1993 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Optical products information (guide for using CD-ROM), 1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Optical technology articles, circa 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Policies and reference, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Policy and planning, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Position descriptions, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Presentation to society for scholarly publishing, "Gatekeeping Revisited", 1990 June 7 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Professional development, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Publication, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      "A vision of the library of the 21st century" by Charlene Hurt
    - Publication, 1995 June 15 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      book review "Advances in library automation and networking" by Charlene Hurt
    - Publication, 1997 February (Box 30, Folder 4)
      "Building library space in the age of virtual libraries" by Charlene Hurt, published in College and Research Libraries News
    - Publication, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      "Charlene"
    - Publication, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      "Collection development strategies for a university center library" by Hurt, Rein, Connors, Walsh and WU
    - Publication, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      "How scholarly communication should work in the 21st century" by Charlene Hurt and Sharon Rogers
    - Publication, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      "Intellectual property in the scholarly communication system" by Charlene Hurt and Sharon Rogers
    - Recasting the university: an introduction, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Reference department memorandums, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Reference general, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Report, "Economic sanctions and international order" by Dr. Miroslav Prokopijevic, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Serial consortium, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Serial consortium, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Solinet fees, 1979-1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Solinet, Atlanta, Georgia, 1995 May 3-5 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Solinet virtual meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, 1996 February 14-16 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Solinet, 1997 April 30-May 2 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Southeastern Library Association and Kentucky Library Association joint conference, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Southeastern Special Collection Access Project (SESCA), 1995 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Space planning information system, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Special collections budget, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Sponsored programs, 1989-1996 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Staff meetings, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Staff retreat, Hemlock overlook, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Statistics, 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Student affairs, 1984-1994 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Student union board meeting minutes, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Summer session catalog, 1984-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Systems office, 1984-1995 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Techlaw Inc., 1993 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Telecom and client support (TCS), 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Telefax agreement, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Tina's presentation to Biology 113, circa 1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - University Center initial planning, 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      1 of 3
    - University Center initial planning, 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      2 of 3
    - University Center initial planning, 1987-1990 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      3 of 3
    - University Center initial planning (3), 1990-1994 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - University Center initial planning (3), 1990-1994 (Box 32, Folder 13)